{
    "subject": "resource/Stomach",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "The stomach is a muscular, hollow, dilated part of the digestive system which functions as an important organ of the digestive tract in many animals, including vertebrates, echinoderms, insects (mid-gut), and molluscs. It is involved in the second phase of digestion, following mastication (chewing).In most vertebrates, the stomach is located between the esophagus and the small intestine. It secretes protein-digesting enzymes called proteases and gastric acid to aid in food digestion, through smooth muscular contractions before sending partially digested food (chyme) to the small intestines.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of Stomach is that it is a muscular, hollow, dilated part of the digestive system which functions as an important organ of the digestive tract in many animals, including vertebrates, echinoderms, insects (mid-gut), and molluscs. It is involved in the second phase of digestion, following mastication (chewing). In most vertebrates, the stomach is located between the esophagus and the small intestine. It secretes protein-digesting enzymes called proteases and gastric acid to aid in food digestion, through smooth muscular contractions before sending partially digested food (chyme) to the small intestines.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7320302724838257,
            "question": "In what animals can we find a stomach as part of their digestive system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6610772013664246,
            "question": "What are the two main components secreted by the stomach to aid digestion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6526856422424316,
            "question": "What type of contractions does the stomach use to aid digestion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6460979580879211,
            "question": "Where is the stomach located in most vertebrates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5880887508392334,
            "question": "What term describes the partially digested food leaving the stomach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5727972984313965,
            "question": "Besides vertebrates, what other types of animals have a stomach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5715650916099548,
            "question": "What is the name of the process that precedes digestion in the stomach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5584241151809692,
            "question": "What part of the digestive system comes *before* the stomach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5285473465919495,
            "question": "What is the primary function of the stomach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4906528890132904,
            "question": "What happens to food after it has been processed by the stomach?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of Stomach is that it is a muscular, hollow, dilated part of the digestive system which functions as an important organ of the digestive tract in many animals, including vertebrates, echinoderms, insects (mid-gut), and molluscs. It is involved in the second phase of digestion, following mastication (chewing). In most vertebrates, the stomach is located between the esophagus and the small intestine. It secretes protein-digesting enzymes called proteases and gastric acid to aid in food digestion, through smooth muscular contractions before sending partially digested food (chyme) to the small intestines.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8538_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary function of the stomach?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8538_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What part of the digestive system comes *before* the stomach?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8538_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the process that precedes digestion in the stomach?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8538_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8538_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Query: The abstract of Stomach is that it is a muscular, hollow, dilated part of the digestive system which functions as an important organ of the digestive tract in many animals, including vertebrates, echinoderms, insects (mid-gut), and molluscs. It is involved in the second phase of digestion, following mastication (chewing). In most vertebrates, the stomach is located between the esophagus and the small intestine. It secretes protein-digesting enzymes called proteases and gastric acid to aid in food digestion, through smooth muscular contractions before sending partially digested food (chyme) to the small intestines.\nResponse: \n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided abstract about the stomach is supported by the documents. The documents describe the stomach as a muscular, hollow organ that aids in digestion and prepares food for passage into the small intestine, which aligns with the description given in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}